Guide to the Jessie Louise Donaldson-Anne Banks Papers 1922-1985
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
- James Willard Schultz's published and unpublished works, 1922-1985; Series 3
  - Publishers - publishing agreement - University of Oklahoma, 1960 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Publishers - royalty statements - Houghton Mifflin Company (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Publishers - royalty statements - others (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Silliman: Betts - exchanged manuscripts by James Willard Schultz (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Silliman: Betts - exchanged manuscripts by James Willard Schultz (cont.) (Box-folder 10/16-18)
  - Silliman: correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Silliman: correspondence: Mountain Press Publishing Co., 1979-1985 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Silliman: correspondence: Other publishers, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Silliman: Floating on the Missouri, drafts of introduction (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Silliman: Floating on the Missouri, carbon copy of draft manuscript (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Silliman: Floating on the Missouri, set of page proofs (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Silliman: Many Strange Characters: Montana Frontier Tales, drafts of introduction (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Silliman: Many Strange Characters: Montana Frontier Tales, drafts of some included stories (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Silliman: Many Strange Characters: Montana Frontier Tales, carbon copy of draft manuscript (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Silliman: Many Strange Characters: Montana Frontier Tales, author/editor galley proof (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Silliman: We Seized Our Rifles: Recollections of the Montana Frontier, drafts of introduction (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Silliman: We Seized Our Rifles, drafts of authors biographic sketches (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Silliman: We Seized Our Rifles, photocopies of published and/or typed drafts of stories (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Silliman: We Seized Our Rifles, carbon copy of draft manuscript (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Silliman: We Seized Our Rifles, carbon copy of draft manuscript (cont.) (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Silliman: Why Gone Those Times? Blackfoot Tales, draft introduction (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Silliman: Why Gone Those Times? Blackfoot Tales, carbon copy of draft manuscript (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Silliman: Why Gone Those Times? Blackfoot Tales, carbon copy of draft manuscript (cont.) (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Silliman: transcriptions of stories not used (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Silliman: photocopies of stories not used (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Silliman: manuscripts of four original short stories by Eugene Lee Silliman (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Silliman: copies of photographs suggested for publications (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Silliman: miscellaneous working papers (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Silliman: papers, agreement, royalty statement - Mountain Press Publishing Co. (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Silliman: publication announcements and newspaper articles (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Original audio tapes: A - HH Restricted *** (Box-folder 13/1)